http://www.botanicalpaperworks.com/terms

Terms Of Use and Privacy Policy
Terms Of Use and Privacy Policy of Botanical PaperWorksTerms of Use
Any member or other user (together defined as “User”) of the Botanicalpaperworks.com website, published by Botanical PaperWorks Inc. (“Botanical PaperWorks”), by using the website, agrees to abide by the Terms of Use contained herein. User agrees to have read and understood the Terms of Use, Privacy and Security Policy before proceeding to use the website. User agrees to abide by all policies and accept all risks stated therein. The Terms of Use explain what User can expect from using the site and identify User’s rights.
Botanical PaperWorks sells wedding favors, invitations, and/or other items through its website. To purchase product, User signs up for an account and purchases product. At any time, at the request of User, Botanical PaperWorks will close User’s account.
User agrees to respect Botanical PaperWorks’ intellectual property and not to reproduce, copy, display, or create derivative works from any item purchased or sent from Botanical PaperWorks, or any visual from the Botanical PaperWorks website without the express written consent of Botanical PaperWorks. User acknowledges that the Botanical PaperWorks website and service contains content and/or parts protected by copyright and patent. User agrees not to copy or mimic the content or service of Botanical PaperWorks without Botanical PaperWorks’ express written consent. User agrees not to export by any means any Botanical PaperWorks’ content or description of any Botanical PaperWorks content or service to any foreign destination.
The Botanical PaperWorks website is designed for the use of adults and/or children under the supervision of adults. Botanical PaperWorks reserves the right to terminate User’s account at any time for any reason or no reason.
All information on this website is provided ‘as is’ without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title or non-infringement. Anyone downloading files from the Botanical PaperWorks website does so at their own risk and assumes the risk of computer viruses or other malicious programs.
In no event shall Botanical PaperWorks be liable to any party for any direct, indirect, special or other consequential damages for any use of this website, or on any other hyper-linked website, including, without limitation, any loss of programs or other data on your computer or otherwise; or products received from Botanical PaperWorks.
Botanical PaperWorks cannot control which websites link to the Botanical PaperWorks website. No such link should be construed as an endorsement by Botanical PaperWorks of any such third-party site.
User agrees that as Botanical PaperWorks is in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, jurisdiction for all disputes regarding Botanical PaperWorks shall be resolved within the Manitoba legal system. User agrees to assert claims exclusively on an individual (non-class) basis.
Privacy Policy
Information Collected
Botanical PaperWorks collects your personal information in the following ways:
When you place an order - We collect only the personal information necessary in order to process and ship your order. All personal information collected by Botanical PaperWorks will be kept confidential and, with the exception of our web developer, will not be disclosed or sold to any third party. We do retain your personal information in order to provide you with fast and efficient service on your future orders. If you are a citizen of the EU, we will only retain your information for as long as necessary to provide the services you have requested or for other such essential purposes such as complying with our legal obligations (including, but not limited to, applicable tax/revenue laws).
When you sign up for our newsletters - We use MailChimp as our marketing automation platform to send you the newsletters you have requested to receive. When you sign up, your information is transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their privacy policy that is available here.
When you use our website - Botanical PaperWorks uses anonymous information from third party sources including social media platforms and a web analytics service. This information pertains to web pages viewed and allows us to analyze trends, track User's movements, provide a better website experience and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Botanical PaperWorks does not use this data in a manner that would identify the User personally.
Payment
User credit card payment is processed in real-time by Moneris Solutions Corporation and their privacy policy is available here. Credit card number, expiry date, and security code are not stored by Botanical PaperWorks.
Security
Botanical PaperWorks takes the security of all personal information seriously and uses reasonable, industry-standard means to ensure the safety of all such information. For example, Botanical PaperWorks uses Secure Sockets Layering, a commonly-used protocol for managing the security of a message transmission on the internet. Botanical PaperWorks also encrypts all the personal information of customers and any other users and stores such information on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access facilities.
User is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of personal information, including username and password; for restricting access to personal computers and mobile devices; and for logging off following the access of public computers and/or any other devices used to access Botanical PaperWorks.
Choice and Control
You can contact us directly to obtain an electronic copy of the personal data we have on file for you, make changes to your personal information or to ask us to delete your personal information (after our legal obligations for holding it have been met).
If you have signed up for one or more of our newsletters, you can update your content preferences to change the newsletters you'd like to receive, or unsubscribe completely using the links at the bottom of each newsletter email.
The Botanical PaperWorks website uses cookies to improve functionality and to support your transactions with us. Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them‚ blocking them‚ or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. You can choose to browse our Site without accepting our Site’s cookies, however without these cookies enabled‚ you may not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain Site features.
Age of Consent
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site. If you believe we have collected information from your child, please contact us so that we can work to delete it.
Privacy Policy Changes
Botanical PaperWorks reserves the right to make changes to this policy at any time, and User should check back for updates from time to time. If such changes materially change User’s terms of use, Botanical PaperWorks will make reasonable effort to contact User. User, by using the website, accepts the terms outlined in this policy. Please contact customer support with any questions or concerns regarding this policy at info@botanicalpaperworks.com.
Third Party Websites
Botanical PaperWorks may provide links to web pages and content of third parties ("Third Party Content") as a service to those interested in this information. Once you leave the Botanical PaperWorks website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies. We suggest that you review the applicable terms and policies, including privacy and data gathering practices, of the sites that you visit.
Botanical PaperWorks does not monitor nor does it have any control over any Third Party Content or third party websites. Botanical PaperWorks does not endorse or adopt any Third Party Content and can make no guarantee as to its accuracy or completeness. Users use these links and Third Party Content contained therein at their own risk.
About Us
About Botanical PaperWorks
Our Eco Commitment
Customer Testimonials
Site Map
Terms Of Use and Privacy Policy
Job Postings
About Plantable Paper
Support for Designers and Printers
I have loved my seed paper tags! My customers have noticed too, adding in that special touch has made a difference and helping to "grow" my business....THANK YOU!
Lauren Stevenson
© Botanical PaperWorks Inc. 2020. All Rights Reserved.
Thank you!
Your order is currently being processed. Please do not hit refresh or leave this page until your order has been successfully submitted, and the confirmation screen has appeared.
